Guide to the Bruce J. Zobel Papers, 1937-2008 MC 00259
Special Collections Research Center
- Education and Teaching, 1952-2001; MC 00259 Series 07; 16.0 Linear feet; 32 boxes
  - Ph.D. Proposals
    - Shelbourne, C.J.A (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Shimizu, Jarbas (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Simmons, Robert (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Sluder, Earl (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Smith, H. Donald (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Sniezko, Richard (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Stahl, Per (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Stonecypher, Roy (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Stubblefield, George (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Taft, Kingsley (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - Talbert, John (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - Taras, Michael (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - Taylor, Fred (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Thorbjornsen, Eyrid (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - Van Wyck, Gerritt (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Veal, Mick (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - Von Weissenberg, Kim (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - Wearstler, Kenneth (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Webb, Charles (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - Weber, J.L. (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - Weir, Robert (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - Wilcox, M.D. (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - Williams, Claire (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Woessner, Ronald (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Masters Theses
    - Baker, J. Keith, 1981 (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - Carter, Allen R., 1979 (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - Clarke, Charles Richard Emlyn, 1990 (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - Contreras Marques, Carlos Enrique, 1997 (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - Deines, James, 1973 (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - Flowers, Willard Russell, 1978 (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - Haught, Aldin, 1958 (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - Jasso Mata, Jesus, 1966 (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - Juarez Martinez, Matias Ricardo, 1983 (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - Kang, Hyun-Chung, 1976 (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - Kikuti, Paulo, 1988 (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - Long, Alan Jack, 1971 (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - Mahalovich, Mary Frances, 1985 (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - McRae, John B., 1981 (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - Mothe, Frederic, 1983 (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - Nalampoon, Anan, 1971 (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - Neale, David Bryan, 1976 (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - Nicholls, Jack William Pellew, 1964 (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - Nicolielo, Norival, 1984 (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - Renbuss, Maija Anna, 1968 (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - Sastry, C.B.R., 1967 (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - Shannon, Michael James, 1966 (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - Slocum, George, 1932 (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - Smith, James Lockard, 1978 (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - Teate, J. Lamar, 1967 (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - Zobel, Donald B., 1965 (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - Balodis, Vilnis, 1987 (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - Barnes, R.D., 1973 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Ph.D. Theses
    - Callaham, Robert Z., 1955 (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - Cech, Franklin Charles, 1958 (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - Clark, Noel Bryan, 1998 (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - Critchfield, William B., 1957 (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - Davidson, John, 1972 (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - DeBarr, Gary L., 1974 (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - Eguiluz Piedra, Teobaldo, 1978 (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - Eldridge, K.G., 1969 (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - Fernando, Luis Osorio, 1999 (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - Foster, George Samuel, Jr., 1983 (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - Goddard, Ray Everett, 1960 (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - Ikemori, Yara Kiemi, 1990 (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - Jasso Mata, Jesus, 1982 (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - Koltzenburg, Christa, 1966 (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - Kress, Lance W., 1978 (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - Lewark, Siegfried, 1981 (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - Mancera Vigueras, Ofelia, 1956 (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - Nanson, Alphonse, 1968 (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - Nicholls, Jack William Pellew, 1976 (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - Olischlager, Klaus, 1969 (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - Polge, Hubert, 1966 (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - Porterfield, Richard L., 1973 (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - Schoenike, Roland E., 1962 (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - Sesbou, Abdessadeck, 1981 (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - Sigurgeirsson, Aoalsteinn, 1992 (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - Sosa Aguilar, Jose Efrain, 1981 (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - Stonecypher, Roy Wesley, 1966 (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - Sziklai, Oscar, 1964 (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - Vincent, Lawrence Wells, 1978 (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - van Buijtenen, Johannes Petrus, 1978 (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - Wakamiya, Izumi, 1994 (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - Zobel, D.B., 1968 (Box 69, Folder 5)
    - Harding, Kevin James, 1995 (Box 380, Folder 6)
    - Gapare, Washington Jingo, 2003 (Box 380, Folder 6)
    - Webb, Charles Donald, 1964 (Box 380, Folder 7)
- Forestry Resources, 1937-2002; MC 00259 Series 08
  The Forestry Resources series contains materials used by Zobel in his research. These materials include research plans and reports, symposia and conference reports, serials, and other publications. Many of these materials are published in languages other than English; some have translations but many do not. During his career, Zobel often discarded pages and chapters unnecessary to his research. Therefore, many items listed here are only partial. Many items were marked by Zobel in the margins or on the cover, offering insight into his research process.
  - Research Plans and Reports, 1937-2002
    - Public Institutions, 1937 (Box 70, Folder 1)
    - Public Institutions, 1952-1955 (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - Public Institutions, 1956-1957 (Box 70, Folder 3)
    - Public Institutions, 1958 (Box 70, Folder 4)
    - Public Institutions, 1959 (Box 70, Folder 5)
    - Public Institutions, 1960-1961 (Box 70, Folder 6)
    - Public Institutions, 1962 (Box 70, Folder 7)
    - Public Institutions, 1963-1964 (Box 70, Folder 8)
    - Public Institutions, 1965-1967 (Box 70, Folder 9)
    - Public Institutions, 1968 (Box 70, Folder 10)
    - Public Institutions, 1969 (Box 70, Folder 11)
    - Public Institutions, 1970 (Box 70, Folder 12)
    - Public Institutions, 1971 (Box 70, Folder 13)
    - Public Institutions, 1973-1974 (Box 70, Folder 14)
    - Public Institutions, 1980 (Box 71, Folder 1)
    - Public Institutions, [no date] (Box 71, Folder 2)
    - Private Industry, 1957-1960 (Box 71, Folder 3)
    - Private Industry, 1961-1968 (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - Private Industry, 1971-1980 (Box 71, Folder 5)
    - Private Industry, [no date] (Box 71, Folder 6)
    - Columbia, 2002 (Box 380, Folder 8)
  - Tree Improvement and Hardwood Cooperatives Publications, 1950-1993
    - Adams - Arnold (Box 71, Folder 7)
    - Balocchi - Barefoot (Box 71, Folder 8)
    - Blair - Brown (Box 71, Folder 9)
    - Cannell - Cole (Box 71, Folder 10)
    - Donahue - Dvorak (Box 71, Folder 11)
    - Eguiluz-Piedra - Frederick, Formerly Box 60A (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - Gardner - Hunt, Formerly Box 60A (Box 72, Folder 2)
    - Jayawickrama - Johnson, Formerly Box 60A (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - Kellison [Folder 1 of 2], Formerly Box 60A (Box 72, Folder 4)
    - Kellison [Folder 2 of 2], Formerly Box 60A (Box 72, Folder 5)
    - Kinloch - Lantz, Formerly Box 60A (Box 72, Folder 6)
    - Leach - Lowerts, Formerly Box 60A (Box 72, Folder 7)
    - Mahalovich - Matziris, Formerly Box 60B (Box 73, Folder 1)
    - McCall - McKeand, Formerly Box 60B (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - Moody - Owino, Formerly Box 60B (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - Pearson - Rockwood, Formerly Box 60B (Box 73, Folder 4)
    - Sax - Shelbourne, Formerly Box 60B (Box 73, Folder 5)
    - Sluder - Sniezko, Formerly Box 60B (Box 73, Folder 6)
    - Sprague - Stonecypher, Formerly Box 60B (Box 73, Folder 7)
    - Talbert - Toda, Formerly Box 60C (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - Wang - Wisniewski, Formerly Box 60C (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - Zobel, 1950-1964; Formerly Box 60C (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - Zobel, 1965-1969; Formerly Box 60C (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - Zobel, 1970-1971; Formerly Box 60C (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - Zobel, 1972; Formerly Box 60C (Box 74, Folder 6)
    - Zobel, 1973; Formerly Box 60C (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - Zobel, 1974; Formerly Box 60D (Box 75, Folder 1)
    - Zobel, 1975; Formerly Box 60D (Box 75, Folder 2)
    - Zobel, 1976-1977; Formerly Box 60D (Box 75, Folder 3)
    - Zobel, 1978; Formerly Box 60D (Box 75, Folder 4)
    - Zobel, 1979; Formerly Box 60D (Box 75, Folder 5)
    - Zobel, 1980; Formerly Box 60D (Box 75, Folder 6)
    - Zobel, 1981-1982; Formerly Box 60D (Box 75, Folder 7)
    - Zobel, 1983-1989; Formerly Box 60D (Box 75, Folder 8)
    - Zobel, 1990-1993; Formerly Box 60D (Box 75, Folder 9)
- Serials, 1965-2000; MC 00259 Series 09
  - Annales de Recherche Sylvicoles (Association Foret-Cellulose), 1973; Formerly Box 60E (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Annales de Recherche Sylvicoles (Association Foret-Cellulose), 1974; Formerly Box 60E (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Annales de Recherche Sylvicoles (Association Foret-Cellulose), 1975; Formerly Box 60E (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Annales de Recherche Sylvicoles (Association Foret-Cellulose), 1977; Formerly Box 60E (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - Annales de Recherche Sylvicoles (Association Foret-Cellulose), 1978; Formerly Box 60E (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - Annales de Recherche Sylvicoles (Association Foret-Cellulose), 1979; Formerly Box 60F (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Annales de Recherche Sylvicoles (Association Foret-Cellulose), 1980; Formerly Box 60F (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Annales de Recherche Sylvicoles (Association Foret-Cellulose), 1981; Formerly Box 60F (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - Annales de Recherche Sylvicoles (Association Foret-Cellulose), 1982; Formerly Box 60F (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - Annales de Recherche Sylvicoles (Association Foret-Cellulose), 1983; Formerly Box 60F (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - Annales de Recherche Sylvicoles (Association Foret-Cellulose), 1984; Formerly Box 60F (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - Annales de Recherche Sylvicoles (Association Foret-Cellulose), 1985; Formerly Box 60G (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Annales de Recherche Sylvicoles (Association Foret-Cellulose), 1986; Formerly Box 60G (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - Annales de Recherche Sylvicoles (Association Foret-Cellulose), 1990; Formerly Box 60G (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - Annali Istituto Sperimentale Selvicoltura (Italy), Volume 1, 1970; Formerly Box 60G (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - Annali Istituto Sperimentale Selvicoltura (Italy), Volume 2, 1971; Formerly Box 60G (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - Annali Istituto Sperimentale Selvicoltura (Italy), Volume 7, 1976; Formerly Box 60G (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - Annali Istituto Sperimentale Selvicoltura (Italy), Volume 8, 1977; Formerly Box 60H (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - Annali Istituto Sperimentale Selvicoltura (Italy), Volume 9, 1978; Formerly Box 60H (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - Annali Istituto Sperimentale Selvicoltura (Italy), Volume 11, 1980; Formerly Box 60H (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - Annali Istituto Sperimentale Selvicoltura (Italy), Volume 12 and 13, 1981-1982; Formerly Box 60H (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - Annali Istituto Sperimentale Selvicoltura (Italy), Volume 14, 1983; Formerly Box 60H (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - Annali Istituto Sperimentale Selvicoltura (Italy), Volume 15, 1984; Formerly Box 60H (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - Annali Istituto Sperimentale Selvicoltura (Italy), Volume 17, 1986; Formerly Box 60I (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - Annali Istituto Sperimentale Selvicoltura (Italy), Volume 20, 1989; Formerly Box 60I (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - Annali Istituto Sperimentale Selvicoltura (Italy), Volume 21, 1990; Formerly Box 60I (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - Annali Istituto Sperimentale Selvicoltura (Italy), Volume 22, 1991; Formerly Box 60I (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - Annali Istituto Sperimentale Selvicoltura (Italy), Volume 23, 1992; Formerly Box 60I (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - Annali Istituto Sperimentale Selvicoltura (Italy), Volume 24, 1993; Formerly Box 60I (Box 80, Folder 6)
  - Annali Istituto Sperimentale Selvicoltura (Italy), Volume 25 and 26, 1994-1995; Formerly Box 60J (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - Annali Istituto Sperimentale Selvicoltura (Italy), Volume 27, 1996; Formerly Box 60J (Box 81, Folder 2)
  - Australian Forest Research, Volume 1, Number 4, 1965; Formerly Box 60J (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - Australian Forest Research, Volume 2, Number 1, 1966; Formerly Box 60J (Box 81, Folder 4)
  - Australian Forest Research, Volume 2, Number 2, 1966; Formerly Box 60J (Box 81, Folder 5)
  - Australian Forest Research, Volume 2, Number 3, 1966; Formerly Box 60J (Box 81, Folder 6)
  - Australian Forest Research, Volume 2, Number 4, 1967; Formerly Box 60J (Box 81, Folder 7)
  - Australian Forest Research, Volume 3, Number 1, 1967; Formerly Box 60J (Box 81, Folder 8)
  - Australian Forest Research, Volume 3, Number 2, 1968; Formerly Box 60J (Box 81, Folder 9)
  - Australian Forest Research, Volume 3, Number 3, 1968; Formerly Box 60J (Box 81, Folder 10)
  - Australian Forest Research, Volume 3, Number 4, 1968; Formerly Box 60J (Box 81, Folder 11)
  - Australian Forest Research, Volume 7, Number 1, 1975; Formerly Box 60J (Box 81, Folder 12)
  - Australian Forest Research Newsletter, Number 4, 1977; Formerly Box 60J (Box 81, Folder 13)
  - Australian Forestry (Journal of the Institute of Forestry of Australia), Volume 30, Number 1, 1966; Formerly Box 60J (Box 81, Folder 14)
  - Australian Forestry (Journal of the Institute of Forestry of Australia), Volume 30, Number 2, 1966; Formerly Box 60J (Box 81, Folder 15)
  - Australian Forestry (Journal of the Institute of Forestry of Australia), Volume 30, Number 3, 1966; Formerly Box 60J (Box 81, Folder 16)
  - Australian Forestry (Journal of the Institute of Forestry of Australia), Volume 30, Number 4, 1966; Formerly Box 60J (Box 81, Folder 17)
  - Australian Forestry (Journal of the Institute of Forestry of Australia), Volume 49, Number 4, 1986; Formerly Box 60J (Box 81, Folder 18)
  - Australian Forestry (Journal of the Institute of Forestry of Australia), Volume 50, Number 2, 1987; Formerly Box 60J (Box 81, Folder 19)
  - Australian Forestry (Journal of the Institute of Forestry of Australia), Volume 50, Number 3, 1987; Formerly Box 60J (Box 81, Folder 20)
  - Avance Forestal (Sociedad de Ingenieros Forestales-Venezuela), Number 6, undated; Formerly Box 60J (Box 81, Folder 21)
  - Boletim de Pesquisa Florestal (Embrapa, Brazil), Number 1, 1980; Formerly Box 60K (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - Boletim de Pesquisa Florestal (Embrapa, Brazil), Number 2, 1981; Formerly Box 60K (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - Boletim Technico (Instituto Brasileiro de Desenvolvimento Florestal), Number 5, 1978; Formerly Box 60K (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - Boletim Technico (Instituto Brasileiro de Desenvolvimento Florestal), Number 6, 1981; Formerly Box 60K (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - Boletim Technico (Instituto Brasileiro de Desenvolvimento Florestal), Number 7, 1982; Formerly Box 60K (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - Boletim Technico (Instituto Brasileiro de Desenvolvimento Florestal), Number 8, 1984; Formerly Box 60K (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - Boletim Tecnico (Sociedade de Investigacoes Florestais), Number 3, 1981; Formerly Box 60K (Box 82, Folder 7)
  - Boletim Tecnico (Sociedade de Investigacoes Florestais), Number 5, 1981; Formerly Box 60K (Box 82, Folder 8)
  - Boletim Tecnico (Sociedade de Investigacoes Florestais), Number 7, 1981; Formerly Box 60K (Box 82, Folder 9)
  - Boletim Tecnico (Sociedade de Investigacoes Florestais), Numero Especial, 1980; Formerly Box 60K (Box 82, Folder 10)
  - Boletim Tecnico (Sociedade de Investigacoes Florestais), Volume 2, Numero Especial, 1979; Formerly Box 60K (Box 82, Folder 11)
  - Bosque (Universidade Austral de Chile), Volume 1, Number 1, 1975; Formerly Box 60K (Box 82, Folder 12)
  - Bosque (Universidade Austral de Chile), Volume 1, Number 2, 1976; Formerly Box 60K (Box 82, Folder 13)
  - Bosque (Universidade Austral de Chile), Volume 2, Number 1, 1977; Formerly Box 60K (Box 82, Folder 14)
  - Brasil Florestal (Instituto Brasileiro de Desenvolvimento Florestal), Number 1, 1971; Formerly Box 60K (Box 82, Folder 15)
  - Brasil Florestal (Instituto Brasileiro de Desenvolvimento Florestal), Number 11, 1972; Formerly Box 60K (Box 82, Folder 16)
  - Brasil Florestal (Instituto Brasileiro de Desenvolvimento Florestal), Number 18, 1974; Formerly Box 60K (Box 82, Folder 17)
  - Brasil Florestal (Instituto Brasileiro de Desenvolvimento Florestal), Number 19, 1974; Formerly Box 60K (Box 82, Folder 18)
  - Brasil Florestal (Instituto Brasileiro de Desenvolvimento Florestal), Number 22, 1975; Formerly Box 60K (Box 82, Folder 19)
  - Brasil Florestal (Instituto Brasileiro de Desenvolvimento Florestal), Number 29, 1977; Formerly Box 60K (Box 82, Folder 20)
  - Brasil Florestal (Instituto Brasileiro de Desenvolvimento Florestal), Number 30, 1977; Formerly Box 60K (Box 82, Folder 21)
  - Brasil Florestal (Instituto Brasileiro de Desenvolvimento Florestal), Number 31, 1977; Formerly Box 60K (Box 82, Folder 22)
  - Brasil Florestal (Instituto Brasileiro de Desenvolvimento Florestal), Number 32, 1977; Formerly Box 60K (Box 82, Folder 23)
  - Brasil Florestal (Instituto Brasileiro de Desenvolvimento Florestal), Number 33, 1978; Formerly Box 60L (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - Brasil Florestal (Instituto Brasileiro de Desenvolvimento Florestal), Number 34, 1978; Formerly Box 60L (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - Brasil Florestal (Instituto Brasileiro de Desenvolvimento Florestal), Number 35, 1978; Formerly Box 60L (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - Brasil Florestal (Instituto Brasileiro de Desenvolvimento Florestal), Number 36, 1978; Formerly Box 60L (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - Brasil Florestal (Instituto Brasileiro de Desenvolvimento Florestal), Number 37, 1979; Formerly Box 60L (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - Brasil Florestal (Instituto Brasileiro de Desenvolvimento Florestal), Number 38, 1979; Formerly Box 60L (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - Brasil Florestal (Instituto Brasileiro de Desenvolvimento Florestal), Number 39, 1979; Formerly Box 60L (Box 83, Folder 7)
  - Brasil Florestal (Instituto Brasileiro de Desenvolvimento Florestal), Number 40, 1979; Formerly Box 60L (Box 83, Folder 8)
  - Brasil Florestal (Instituto Brasileiro de Desenvolvimento Florestal), Number 41, 1980; Formerly Box 60L (Box 83, Folder 9)
  - Brasil Florestal (Instituto Brasileiro de Desenvolvimento Florestal), Number 42, 1980; Formerly Box 60L (Box 83, Folder 10)
  - Brasil Florestal (Instituto Brasileiro de Desenvolvimento Florestal), Number 43, 1980; Formerly Box 60L (Box 83, Folder 11)
  - Brasil Florestal (Instituto Brasileiro de Desenvolvimento Florestal), Number 44, 1980; Formerly Box 60L (Box 83, Folder 12)
  - Brasil Florestal (Instituto Brasileiro de Desenvolvimento Florestal), Number 45, 1981; Formerly Box 60L (Box 83, Folder 13)
  - Brasil Florestal (Instituto Brasileiro de Desenvolvimento Florestal), Number 48, 1981; Formerly Box 60L (Box 83, Folder 14)
  - Brasil Florestal (Instituto Brasileiro de Desenvolvimento Florestal), Number 49, 1982; Formerly Box 60L (Box 83, Folder 15)
  - Brasil Florestal (Instituto Brasileiro de Desenvolvimento Florestal), Number 50, 1982; Formerly Box 60L (Box 83, Folder 16)
  - Brasil Florestal (Instituto Brasileiro de Desenvolvimento Florestal), Number 51, 1982; Formerly Box 60L (Box 83, Folder 17)
  - Brasil Florestal (Instituto Brasileiro de Desenvolvimento Florestal), Number 52, 1982; Formerly Box 60L (Box 83, Folder 18)
  - Brasil Florestal (Instituto Brasileiro de Desenvolvimento Florestal), Number 53, 1983; Formerly Box 60L (Box 83, Folder 19)
  - Brasil Florestal (Instituto Brasileiro de Desenvolvimento Florestal), Number 54, 1983; Formerly Box 60L (Box 83, Folder 20)
  - Brasil Florestal (Instituto Brasileiro de Desenvolvimento Florestal), Number 55, 1983; Formerly Box 60L (Box 83, Folder 21)
  - Brasil Florestal (Instituto Brasileiro de Desenvolvimento Florestal), Number 56, 1983; Formerly Box 60L (Box 83, Folder 22)
  - Brasil Florestal (Instituto Brasileiro de Desenvolvimento Florestal), Number 57, 1984; Formerly Box 60L (Box 83, Folder 23)
  - Brasil Florestal (Instituto Brasileiro de Desenvolvimento Florestal), Number 60, 1984; Formerly Box 60L (Box 83, Folder 24)
  - Brasil Florestal (Instituto Brasileiro de Desenvolvimento Florestal), Number 61, 1987; Formerly Box 60L (Box 83, Folder 25)
  - Brasil Florestal (Instituto Brasileiro de Desenvolvimento Florestal), Number 62, 1987; Formerly Box 60L (Box 83, Folder 26)
  - Brasil Florestal (Instituto Brasileiro de Desenvolvimento Florestal), Number 63, 1988; Formerly Box 60L (Box 83, Folder 27)
  - Brasil Florestal (Instituto Brasileiro de Desenvolvimento Florestal), Number 66, 1988; Formerly Box 60L (Box 83, Folder 28)
  - Breeding Pinus Radiata (IUFRO Working Party S2-03-09), Number 1, 1977; Formerly Box 60M (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - Breeding Pinus Radiata (IUFRO Working Party S2-03-09), Number 2, 1978; Formerly Box 60M (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - Breeding Pinus Radiata (IUFRO Working Party S2-03-09), Number 3, 1979; Formerly Box 60M (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - Breeding Pinus Radiata (IUFRO Working Party S2-03-09), Number 4, 1980; Formerly Box 60M (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - Bulletin of the Forest Tree Breeding Institute (Japan), Number 2, 1984; Formerly Box 60M (Box 84, Folder 5)
  - Bulletin of the Forest Tree Breeding Institute (Japan), Number 8, 1990; Formerly Box 60M (Box 84, Folder 6)
  - Bulletin of the Forest Tree Breeding Institute (Japan), Number 11, 1993; Formerly Box 60M (Box 84, Folder 7)
  - Bulletin of the Forest Tree Breeding Institute (Japan), Number 12, 1994; Formerly Box 60M (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - Bulletin of the Forest Tree Breeding Institute (Japan), Number 13, 1995; Formerly Box 60M (Box 84, Folder 9)
  - Bulletin of the Forest Tree Breeding Institute (Japan), Number 14, 1996; Formerly Box 60M (Box 84, Folder 10)
  - Bulletin of the Forest Tree Breeding Institute (Japan), Number 15, 1998; Formerly Box 60M (Box 84, Folder 11)
  - Bulletin of the Forestry and Forest Products Research Institute, Number 310, 1980; Formerly Box 60M (Box 84, Folder 12)
  - Bulletin of the Tokyo University Forests, Number 54, 1958; Formerly Box 60M (Box 84, Folder 13)
  - Bulletin of the Tokyo University Forests, Number 55, 1959; Formerly Box 60M (Box 84, Folder 14)
  - Bulletin of the Tokyo University Forests, Number 99, 1998; Formerly Box 60M (Box 84, Folder 15)
  - CATIE: Nota Tecnica Sobre Manejo de Semillas Forestales Numbers 56-70, March-April 11 (Box 381, Folder 1)
  - CATIE: Nota Tecnica Sobre Manejo de Semillas Forestales, Numbers 102-116, July 2000 (Box 381, Folder 2)
  - Ciencia Forestal (Revista del Instituto Nacional de Investigaciones Forestales - Mexico), Volume 2, Number 6, 1977; Formerly Box 60M (Box 84, Folder 16)
  - Ciencia Forestal (Revista del Instituto Nacional de Investigaciones Forestales - Mexico), Volume 8, Number 41, 1983; Formerly Box 60M (Box 84, Folder 17)
  - Dasonomia Mexicana (Organo Informativo de la Academia Nacional de Ciencias Forestales A.C.), Volume 3, Number 6, 1985; Formerly Box 60N (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - Fitopatologia Brasileira (Sociedade Brasileira de Fitopatologia) Volume 1, Number 3, 1976; Formerly Box 60N (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - Folia Forestalia, No. 433, 1980 (Box 381, Folder 3)
  - Forest Genetic Resources Information (Food and Agriculture Organization of the United Nations), Number 1, 1973; Formerly Box 60N (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - Forest Genetic Resources Information (Food and Agriculture Organization of the United Nations), Number 2, 1973; Formerly Box 60N (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Forest Genetic Resources Information (Food and Agriculture Organization of the United Nations), Number 3, 1974; Formerly Box 60N (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Forest Genetic Resources Information (Food and Agriculture Organization of the United Nations), Number 4, 1975; Formerly Box 60N (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - Forest Genetic Resources Information (Food and Agriculture Organization of the United Nations), Number 5, 1976; Formerly Box 60N (Box 85, Folder 7)
  - Forest Genetic Resources Information (Food and Agriculture Organization of the United Nations), Number 6, 1977; Formerly Box 60N (Box 85, Folder 8)
  - Forest Genetic Resources Information (Food and Agriculture Organization of the United Nations), Number 7, 1978; Formerly Box 60N (Box 85, Folder 9)
  - Forest Genetic Resources Information (Food and Agriculture Organization of the United Nations), Number 8, 1978; Formerly Box 60N (Box 85, Folder 10)